<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en-US" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <id>tag:www.producthunt.com,2005:/feed</id>
  <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.producthunt.com"/>
  <link rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" href="https://www.producthunt.com/feed"/>
  <title>Product Hunt — The best new products, every day</title>
  <updated>2020-11-12T06:30:10-08:00</updated>
  <entry>
    <id>tag:www.producthunt.com,2005:Post/274635</id>
    <published>2020-11-12T06:30:10-08:00</published>
    <updated>2020-11-12T10:09:52-08:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/alexa-care-hub"/>
    <title>Alexa Care Hub — Check in on older relatives</title>
    <content type="html">      &lt;p&gt;
        &amp;#8220;
        I think getting the older generation to adopt this might be a challenge. I would love this for my grandma but she'll just either ignore it or forget how to use Alexa 😅
        &amp;#8221;
        &lt;br&gt;
        – Gabe Perez
      &lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;
        &lt;a href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/alexa-care-hub?utm_campaign=producthunt-atom-posts-feed&amp;amp;utm_medium=rss-feed&amp;amp;utm_source=producthunt-atom-posts-feed"&gt;Discussion&lt;/a&gt;
        |
        &lt;a href="https://www.producthunt.com/r/8637008214b3a3/274635?app_id=339"&gt;Link&lt;/a&gt;
      &lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    <author>
      <name>Gabe Perez</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>tag:www.producthunt.com,2005:Post/274624</id>
    <published>2020-11-12T05:32:28-08:00</published>
    <updated>2020-11-12T12:41:33-08:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/company-forensics-2"/>
    <title>Company Forensics — Learn from the mistakes of VC-funded startups</title>
    <content type="html">      &lt;p&gt;
        &amp;#8220;
        Hi everyone! It's great to be back on ProductHunt. 

We launched the first Company Forensics case study about a year, ago, and ever since we've published 50+ stories of these startup's mistakes. I can't help thinking that there's a bit of schadenfreude involved for everyone watching, listening, or reading. 

Forensics has evolved into a blog, a podcast, and of course the Youtube Channel, which now gets 1MM+ views every month just for our Forensics videos. 

Thanks to everyone who already watched and shared, and welcome everyone who is discovering us today.
        &amp;#8221;
        &lt;br&gt;
        – Caya
      &lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;
        &lt;a href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/company-forensics-2?utm_campaign=producthunt-atom-posts-feed&amp;amp;utm_medium=rss-feed&amp;amp;utm_source=producthunt-atom-posts-feed"&gt;Discussion&lt;/a&gt;
        |
        &lt;a href="https://www.producthunt.com/r/0705070b7bb2a1/274624?app_id=339"&gt;Link&lt;/a&gt;
      &lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    <author>
      <name>Caya</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>tag:www.producthunt.com,2005:Post/274607</id>
    <published>2020-11-12T02:04:34-08:00</published>
    <updated>2020-11-12T12:29:03-08:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/autumn-3"/>
    <title>Autumn — Swipe to shop across +5,000 online stores</title>
    <content type="html">      &lt;p&gt;
        &lt;a href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/autumn-3?utm_campaign=producthunt-atom-posts-feed&amp;amp;utm_medium=rss-feed&amp;amp;utm_source=producthunt-atom-posts-feed"&gt;Discussion&lt;/a&gt;
        |
        &lt;a href="https://www.producthunt.com/r/d7dbfe5197ed4e/274607?app_id=339"&gt;Link&lt;/a&gt;
      &lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    <author>
      <name>Kevin William David</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>tag:www.producthunt.com,2005:Post/274601</id>
    <published>2020-11-12T01:21:05-08:00</published>
    <updated>2020-11-12T11:49:44-08:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/the-orb-by-streamplate"/>
    <title>The Orb by Streamplate — A floating payment terminal that's perfectly spherical.</title>
    <content type="html">      &lt;p&gt;
        &amp;#8220;
        Hey! I'm the Founder/CEO of Streamplate and we're building a personalised food ordering app with health tracking which you can learn more about there - https://www.streampate.com.

The goal of Streamplate is to serve choice, and so we've been working on a massive app that supports a range of features like pre-ordering, at-table ordering, nutrition filtering, curations, events and much more. But we realised that this only one side of the story - the other half is supporting venues on the platform. 

Today, venues really only need one piece of hardware - a payment terminal. Other apps might offer 'in-depth data analytics' or 'discounts' that might incentivise a venue to join, but we don't believe these type of add-ons provide long-term value to venues. Instead, we think the best way to support venues is to ensure that they have the best payment terminal possible. 

Payment terminals aren't designed to be memorable, and it's often the last interaction a customer has with a venue. We've flipped this, and built The Orb which has a lasting impression on the customer. 

The idea is simple: as the customer approaches The Orb, it starts to float.
        &amp;#8221;
        &lt;br&gt;
        – Bryan Jordan
      &lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;
        &lt;a href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/the-orb-by-streamplate?utm_campaign=producthunt-atom-posts-feed&amp;amp;utm_medium=rss-feed&amp;amp;utm_source=producthunt-atom-posts-feed"&gt;Discussion&lt;/a&gt;
        |
        &lt;a href="https://www.producthunt.com/r/feab2d27724ab8/274601?app_id=339"&gt;Link&lt;/a&gt;
      &lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    <author>
      <name>Bryan Jordan</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>tag:www.producthunt.com,2005:Post/274595</id>
    <published>2020-11-12T00:14:07-08:00</published>
    <updated>2020-11-12T11:31:34-08:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/authenteq-2-0"/>
    <title>Authenteq 2.0 — Automated identity verification in under 45 seconds</title>
    <content type="html">      &lt;p&gt;
        &amp;#8220;
        Life is now lived digitally. Whether it’s opening a bank account, renting a property, or protecting your identity online, companies and consumers alike need to onboard swiftly and safely. We believe that identity verification should be fast, secure and accessible for everyone. Our aim is to make Authenteq the most accurate and least memorable part of the customer journey; when our customers can onboard their users with full confidence, then we’ve done our job. 

Here are a couple more things you should know: 

- With us you can fully automate your ID verification, KYC and AML process. No manual busywork 🐝
- The verification will take approximately 45 seconds. From start to finish. Did you see my smiling face in one of our very professional verification videos? 📹
- We strive for frictionless experience  to make sure that you minimise your drop-off rates, not profits! 📈
- Our team is always there to support you because we know that everyone is different and some of us need more support than others. That’s why you can always ask our Integration Manager Derek and his team for help 🦸‍♂️ 🦸‍♀️
- Authenteq’s superhuman AI is always learning to efficiently prevent fraudsters. Think of us like a Superhero of Identity Security 🤖

Ping me if you have any questions or remarks. We’re here to listen. 👂
In the meanwhile; Get Authenteq - identity verification your customers will love 😍 😍 😍
        &amp;#8221;
        &lt;br&gt;
        – Matt Aberdein
      &lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;
        &lt;a href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/authenteq-2-0?utm_campaign=producthunt-atom-posts-feed&amp;amp;utm_medium=rss-feed&amp;amp;utm_source=producthunt-atom-posts-feed"&gt;Discussion&lt;/a&gt;
        |
        &lt;a href="https://www.producthunt.com/r/a2ba171a288126/274595?app_id=339"&gt;Link&lt;/a&gt;
      &lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    <author>
      <name>Matt Aberdein</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>tag:www.producthunt.com,2005:Post/274594</id>
    <published>2020-11-12T00:13:55-08:00</published>
    <updated>2020-11-12T12:39:47-08:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/hunter-templates"/>
    <title>Hunter Templates — Collection of best-performing cold email templates</title>
    <content type="html">      &lt;p&gt;
        &lt;a href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/hunter-templates?utm_campaign=producthunt-atom-posts-feed&amp;amp;utm_medium=rss-feed&amp;amp;utm_source=producthunt-atom-posts-feed"&gt;Discussion&lt;/a&gt;
        |
        &lt;a href="https://www.producthunt.com/r/3f1bdc2089d782/274594?app_id=339"&gt;Link&lt;/a&gt;
      &lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    <author>
      <name>François Grante</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>tag:www.producthunt.com,2005:Post/274593</id>
    <published>2020-11-12T00:06:06-08:00</published>
    <updated>2020-11-12T12:26:31-08:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/saas-funding-report-for-october-2020"/>
    <title>SaaS Funding Report for October 2020 — Report featuring 141 companies and $1.6 Billion of funding</title>
    <content type="html">      &lt;p&gt;
        &amp;#8220;
        Hello Everyone! For the decade, I've been consulting (growth and revenue) for SaaS companies (US, Canada, Germany, and India), and I realize that most of the early-stage SaaS companies struggle with growth, talent, and access to capital. While there are tons of content out there, it's either unstructured (eg: SaaS marketing), non-comprehensive (eg: SaaS growth never accounts for engineering), and promotes a preferential school of thought (eg: lean, PLG). 

That's why a few of us (SaaS founders and me) decided to start a dedicated network (community + resources + jobs + access to investors) for SaaS founders and leaders. 

SaaS Network connects global SaaS founders, executives, investors, and professionals to collaborate mutually, learn, grow, and build scalable and sustainable SaaS companies for the greater good. 

We are launching soon! 

This report is a part of our ongoing offering at the SaaS Network. If you are interested to join the network to tune into SaaS insights and resources, connect with SaaS founders and leaders, and access investors, just reply back, I'll be sure to add you to our early access (FREE) program. 

*if for some reason - the button does not work for you please email me at joseph@saasnetwork.co 🌟


Thank you 🙏
        &amp;#8221;
        &lt;br&gt;
        – Joseph Abraham
      &lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;
        &lt;a href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/saas-funding-report-for-october-2020?utm_campaign=producthunt-atom-posts-feed&amp;amp;utm_medium=rss-feed&amp;amp;utm_source=producthunt-atom-posts-feed"&gt;Discussion&lt;/a&gt;
        |
        &lt;a href="https://www.producthunt.com/r/8ca70ea45fc2f9/274593?app_id=339"&gt;Link&lt;/a&gt;
      &lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    <author>
      <name>Joseph Abraham</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>tag:www.producthunt.com,2005:Post/274592</id>
    <published>2020-11-12T00:04:36-08:00</published>
    <updated>2020-11-12T09:56:10-08:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/app-digger"/>
    <title>App Digger — Cross-country mobile app comparison and analysis tool.</title>
    <content type="html">      &lt;p&gt;
        &amp;#8220;
        Hey Product Hunt!

I am super excited to launch appdigger.co today!

AppDigger 🔨 a platform that helps you get country basis information from an app.

Why we build AppDigger? 🤔

Getting information regarding ranking is always a problem. Also, tracking a competition app for understanding pricing, language, or region strategy is another headache. The region changing from the AppStore to get information from other regions/country is an annoying circumstance.

But now you have a tool! 🎉 

Just type the app or app publisher name to the search click the app from the result and select the target region/country or select as continents AppDigger will get impressive data from selected countries/regions.
You will see the following information from the selected country;
Rating, Reviews, App Prices, In-App Prices, Localize Title, Localized Sub Title, Localized Description, Editor Choice, Previews, etc.

The most demanding feature is Ranking information! 👌
Just imagine you can see all ranging information for 85 different countries, AppDigger allows you to do that, regarding this data you can find out how much popular is the app. Also, you can decide on the growth strategy.

Notices:
This version is the first version of appdigger.co still working on new incoming features.
With the first version, AppDigger only allows IOS apps, working for google play store app implementation.

For the first release, we have unlocked 17 different countries.

Feel free to reach me out to ask or enhance production.
Looking forward to hearing news from you! 😍
        &amp;#8221;
        &lt;br&gt;
        – Ugur Erdal
      &lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;
        &lt;a href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/app-digger?utm_campaign=producthunt-atom-posts-feed&amp;amp;utm_medium=rss-feed&amp;amp;utm_source=producthunt-atom-posts-feed"&gt;Discussion&lt;/a&gt;
        |
        &lt;a href="https://www.producthunt.com/r/c343d7c4581eaa/274592?app_id=339"&gt;Link&lt;/a&gt;
      &lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    <author>
      <name>Ugur Erdal</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>tag:www.producthunt.com,2005:Post/274590</id>
    <published>2020-11-12T00:00:07-08:00</published>
    <updated>2020-11-12T12:39:03-08:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/polybox-email-templates"/>
    <title>Polybox Email Templates — Solution for email creating in coded templates and modules</title>
    <content type="html">      &lt;p&gt;
        &amp;#8220;
        Heeey!

Email Templates to your attention 🔥

If you send newsletters, want to inform your customers about releases, or offer them discounts you have to take a look at Polybox.

Our team deals with newsletters every week, so it’s kind of routine. We understand how it can be annoying to waste time on things that can be made for a couple of minutes per week 📬 Guys, Polybox already has emails you were going to create yourself 😉
 
Polybox includes 20 ready-to-use email templates, just paste your content to make them unique 📝

Want to discover your own style? More than 100 separate modules, from headers, and e-commerce block, to footers, and CTA. Create something special and beautiful by mixing them 💪 

Polybox is based on design system, and the main thing is optimized and clean code, so it’s easy to work with even for your manager 🤓😄  

Guys, no more words, just try them yourself 👊  

Btw, check out our 11.11 SALE page on the website to get -30% for Craftwork UX/UI assets. Take a time before November 14.   

Let us know in the comments below, are you interested in such templates? It’s the first email product we made, so your feedback is really important ❤️ Thanks!
        &amp;#8221;
        &lt;br&gt;
        – Anastasiya Yavorskaya
      &lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;
        &lt;a href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/polybox-email-templates?utm_campaign=producthunt-atom-posts-feed&amp;amp;utm_medium=rss-feed&amp;amp;utm_source=producthunt-atom-posts-feed"&gt;Discussion&lt;/a&gt;
        |
        &lt;a href="https://www.producthunt.com/r/1b763fcfb06e19/274590?app_id=339"&gt;Link&lt;/a&gt;
      &lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    <author>
      <name>Anastasiya Yavorskaya</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>tag:www.producthunt.com,2005:Post/274575</id>
    <published>2020-11-11T20:50:10-08:00</published>
    <updated>2020-11-12T12:41:20-08:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/freehand-template-gallery"/>
    <title>Freehand Template Gallery — Whiteboard templates by innovative leaders.</title>
    <content type="html">      &lt;p&gt;
        &amp;#8220;
        Hey folks,
 
Today, I’m excited to announce a major update to Freehand, our real-time collaborative whiteboard—the &lt;a href="https://www.invisionapp.com/freehand/templates?utm_source=producthunt&amp;amp;utm_medium=producthunt&amp;amp;utm_campaign=gallery_all" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer"&gt;Freehand template gallery&lt;/a&gt;.
 
We’ve partnered with industry leaders in design, product management, marketing, and engineering to bring you the best, proven frameworks for your ideation process, research, strategy sessions, and more. A few of my favorite templates include:

- &lt;a href="https://www.invisionapp.com/freehand/templates/detail/brainstorming-template?utm_source=producthunt&amp;amp;utm_medium=producthunt&amp;amp;utm_campaign=gallery_xbox" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer"&gt;Brainstorming &lt;/a&gt; from &lt;b&gt;Xbox&lt;/b&gt;
- &lt;a href="https://www.invisionapp.com/freehand/templates/detail/customer-journey-map-template?utm_source=producthunt&amp;amp;utm_medium=producthunt&amp;amp;utm_campaign=gallery_amex" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer"&gt;Customer journey map &lt;/a&gt; from &lt;b&gt;American Express&lt;/b&gt;
- &lt;a href="https://www.invisionapp.com/freehand/templates/detail/product-launch-template?utm_source=producthunt&amp;amp;utm_medium=producthunt&amp;amp;utm_campaign=gallery_ld" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer"&gt;Product launch planning &lt;/a&gt; from &lt;b&gt;LaunchDarkly&lt;/b&gt;
- &lt;a href="https://www.invisionapp.com/freehand/templates/detail/sprint-planning-template?utm_source=producthunt&amp;amp;utm_medium=producthunt&amp;amp;utm_campaign=gallery_atlassian" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer"&gt;Agile sprint planning &lt;/a&gt; from &lt;b&gt;Atlassian&lt;/b&gt;
- &lt;a href="https://www.invisionapp.com/freehand/templates/detail/affinity-diagram-template?utm_source=producthunt&amp;amp;utm_medium=producthunt&amp;amp;utm_campaign=gallery_ut" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer"&gt;Affinity diagram &lt;/a&gt; from &lt;b&gt;UserTesting&lt;/b&gt;
 
You can use these templates out of the box or iterate on each template and make them your own. There’s no better way to give everyone a voice when you’re brainstorming, critiquing, sprinting, or aligning as a team.
 
And we’d love to hear your feedback! What templates work well for you? What templates would you like to see added in the future? What are the most effective ways your team is using digital whiteboards in the era of remote work?
        &amp;#8221;
        &lt;br&gt;
        – Clark Valberg
      &lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;
        &lt;a href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/freehand-template-gallery?utm_campaign=producthunt-atom-posts-feed&amp;amp;utm_medium=rss-feed&amp;amp;utm_source=producthunt-atom-posts-feed"&gt;Discussion&lt;/a&gt;
        |
        &lt;a href="https://www.producthunt.com/r/4d3363472496e6/274575?app_id=339"&gt;Link&lt;/a&gt;
      &lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    <author>
      <name>Clark Valberg</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>tag:www.producthunt.com,2005:Post/274574</id>
    <published>2020-11-11T20:43:27-08:00</published>
    <updated>2020-11-12T12:41:05-08:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/on-deck-venture-capital-fellowship-2"/>
    <title>On Deck Venture Capital Fellowship — A high-trust network of top venture capitalists</title>
    <content type="html">      &lt;p&gt;
        &amp;#8220;
        We've had a busy few months at On Deck! The &lt;a href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/the-on-deck-fellowship" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer"&gt;On Deck Founder Fellowship&lt;/a&gt; (ODF) launched around 1.5 years ago, with nearly 1,300 talented Fellows and alumni joining to participate in the program, exploring "what's next" among cohorts of their peers —&amp;nbsp;starting hundreds of companies; and raising well over $200M of angel and seed capital to date.

Lately, we've been thinking about how to serve these founders and "explorers" even better —&amp;nbsp;building &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/david__booth/status/1326279429169901568" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer"&gt;adjacent communities&lt;/a&gt; create mutual value for each other as they grow. 

After launching the &lt;a href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/on-deck-angel-fellowship" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer"&gt;On Deck Angel Fellowship&lt;/a&gt; ("ODA") in August, we had a lot of interest from VCs looking for the same supportive community of peers, and to be plugged into the On Deck community. Today, we're excited to share what eventuated: an experiment with a small group of 50 of the best investors in the world, who have come together twice per week for the past month to meet, share knowledge, and learn from each other.

We're now opening up applications for a second cohort starting in January! 

We ask that participants make a minimum $10k contribution to the &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/beondeck/status/1309563121950838789" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer"&gt;On Deck Access Fund&lt;/a&gt;. The Access Fund is a donor advised fund dedicated to supporting underserved talent in tech, powered by &lt;a href="https://overflow.co/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer"&gt;overflow.co&lt;/a&gt;. Thank you cohort #1 for your generosity!
        &amp;#8221;
        &lt;br&gt;
        – David Booth
      &lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;
        &lt;a href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/on-deck-venture-capital-fellowship-2?utm_campaign=producthunt-atom-posts-feed&amp;amp;utm_medium=rss-feed&amp;amp;utm_source=producthunt-atom-posts-feed"&gt;Discussion&lt;/a&gt;
        |
        &lt;a href="https://www.producthunt.com/r/a24394c97e926c/274574?app_id=339"&gt;Link&lt;/a&gt;
      &lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    <author>
      <name>David Booth</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>tag:www.producthunt.com,2005:Post/274573</id>
    <published>2020-11-11T20:41:22-08:00</published>
    <updated>2020-11-12T12:29:34-08:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/innertrends-2"/>
    <title>InnerTrends — Solve growth challenges without being a data scientist</title>
    <content type="html">      &lt;p&gt;
        &amp;#8220;
        Do you easily get lost all of the noise of your product data like I do? 

I’m not sure about you but I don’t have the skillsets or time to  juggle events, metrics, segments, cohorts, filters, dimensions and visualizations; just to find an insight within my product analytics tool.

On top of that I have to make sure I am collecting right data and it’s cleaned and validated enough to make growth decisions.  

This is why I recommend InnerTrends. It’s the only product analytics + data science tool for software companies that helps solve your biggest growth challenge and algorithmically finds and validates new growth opportunities without having to be a data science expert!
        &amp;#8221;
        &lt;br&gt;
        – Nichole Elizabeth DeMeré
      &lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;
        &lt;a href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/innertrends-2?utm_campaign=producthunt-atom-posts-feed&amp;amp;utm_medium=rss-feed&amp;amp;utm_source=producthunt-atom-posts-feed"&gt;Discussion&lt;/a&gt;
        |
        &lt;a href="https://www.producthunt.com/r/774a4d6ba79a55/274573?app_id=339"&gt;Link&lt;/a&gt;
      &lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    <author>
      <name>Nichole Elizabeth DeMeré</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>tag:www.producthunt.com,2005:Post/274568</id>
    <published>2020-11-11T18:28:20-08:00</published>
    <updated>2020-11-12T12:35:37-08:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/picter"/>
    <title>Picter — The one-stop solution for visual collaboration and review</title>
    <content type="html">      &lt;p&gt;
        &lt;a href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/picter?utm_campaign=producthunt-atom-posts-feed&amp;amp;utm_medium=rss-feed&amp;amp;utm_source=producthunt-atom-posts-feed"&gt;Discussion&lt;/a&gt;
        |
        &lt;a href="https://www.producthunt.com/r/9ef159bfd2cf93/274568?app_id=339"&gt;Link&lt;/a&gt;
      &lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    <author>
      <name>Leon Kirchlechner</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>tag:www.producthunt.com,2005:Post/274563</id>
    <published>2020-11-11T17:09:23-08:00</published>
    <updated>2020-11-12T12:29:44-08:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/instavia"/>
    <title>Instavia — Instant checkout links to sell on social media</title>
    <content type="html">      &lt;p&gt;
        &amp;#8220;
        Hi Product Hunt, 

We are super excited to share the instant checkout links with you. 

It's a simple solution for the ones who hate complexity but want fast results. 

Integrate your stripe account with a one click. 
Create a product &amp;amp; a link in less than 30 seconds and paste it or share it.

Customers clicking the links are taken directly to checkout page.No passwords or login necessary. We support payment with credit cards, apple pay and google pay.

We’d love for you to check it out and let us know what you think!
        &amp;#8221;
        &lt;br&gt;
        – David Parker
      &lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;
        &lt;a href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/instavia?utm_campaign=producthunt-atom-posts-feed&amp;amp;utm_medium=rss-feed&amp;amp;utm_source=producthunt-atom-posts-feed"&gt;Discussion&lt;/a&gt;
        |
        &lt;a href="https://www.producthunt.com/r/47327338ba0b49/274563?app_id=339"&gt;Link&lt;/a&gt;
      &lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    <author>
      <name>David Parker</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>tag:www.producthunt.com,2005:Post/274551</id>
    <published>2020-11-11T14:08:46-08:00</published>
    <updated>2020-11-12T12:39:49-08:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/super-creative-radio"/>
    <title>Super Creative Radio — Nonstop curated music for creative work</title>
    <content type="html">      &lt;p&gt;
        &lt;a href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/super-creative-radio?utm_campaign=producthunt-atom-posts-feed&amp;amp;utm_medium=rss-feed&amp;amp;utm_source=producthunt-atom-posts-feed"&gt;Discussion&lt;/a&gt;
        |
        &lt;a href="https://www.producthunt.com/r/8a25491a9bc76a/274551?app_id=339"&gt;Link&lt;/a&gt;
      &lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    <author>
      <name>Farbod Saraf</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>tag:www.producthunt.com,2005:Post/274550</id>
    <published>2020-11-11T13:54:58-08:00</published>
    <updated>2020-11-12T12:40:10-08:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/rippling-peo"/>
    <title>Rippling PEO — Get better HR &amp; health coverage for up to 30% less</title>
    <content type="html">      &lt;p&gt;
        &lt;a href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/rippling-peo?utm_campaign=producthunt-atom-posts-feed&amp;amp;utm_medium=rss-feed&amp;amp;utm_source=producthunt-atom-posts-feed"&gt;Discussion&lt;/a&gt;
        |
        &lt;a href="https://www.producthunt.com/r/d04b6415262206/274550?app_id=339"&gt;Link&lt;/a&gt;
      &lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    <author>
      <name>Lindsay Amos</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>tag:www.producthunt.com,2005:Post/274544</id>
    <published>2020-11-11T12:03:33-08:00</published>
    <updated>2020-11-12T12:40:13-08:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/craft-docs"/>
    <title>Craft Docs — Cross-platform AppleOS document editor built with Catalyst</title>
    <content type="html">      &lt;p&gt;
        &amp;#8220;
        This is exciting — a really amazing looking cross-platform AppleOS document editor — built with Catalyst.
        &amp;#8221;
        &lt;br&gt;
        – Chris Messina
      &lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;
        &lt;a href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/craft-docs?utm_campaign=producthunt-atom-posts-feed&amp;amp;utm_medium=rss-feed&amp;amp;utm_source=producthunt-atom-posts-feed"&gt;Discussion&lt;/a&gt;
        |
        &lt;a href="https://www.producthunt.com/r/25aa91d213e265/274544?app_id=339"&gt;Link&lt;/a&gt;
      &lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    <author>
      <name>Chris Messina</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>tag:www.producthunt.com,2005:Post/274542</id>
    <published>2020-11-11T11:48:25-08:00</published>
    <updated>2020-11-12T12:40:16-08:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/hero-trainer-2"/>
    <title>Hero Trainer — Game rewards for steps</title>
    <content type="html">      &lt;p&gt;
        &amp;#8220;
        Heroes of Product Hunt,

Problem:
As a gamer, I always found it hard to stay motivated to exercise. Any time I spent away from the game felt like a waste. My character’s level and gear meant more to me than my own health. 

That's why I built Hero Trainer, a free mobile app for gamers. It is the only app where you can use your steps for in-game currency or a full game. 

It keeps you focused on your game while you get healthy. 

Features:
- Not Your Wii Fit: This will never get boring. Your steps will always count towards that next exciting game regardless of game platform. 
- Meet Gamers Into Fitness: Chat and meet gamers from all walks of life: a former NFL player, an eSports host, and ANW Competitor to mention a few.   
- 1UP Motivation: From leveling up heroes to completing quests to challenging guilds to keeping your daily streak, we've made it fun to stay fit. 

How it works: 
- Earn Aura for each step tracked on Apple Health or Google Fit.
- Trade Aura for in-game currency or a full game entirely.

Skip the Waitlist:
Hero Trainer is an invite-only app to maintain a healthy supply of rewards for our users. For this week, everyone who signs-up will directly get to use the app.
        &amp;#8221;
        &lt;br&gt;
        – Yash Jain
      &lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;
        &lt;a href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/hero-trainer-2?utm_campaign=producthunt-atom-posts-feed&amp;amp;utm_medium=rss-feed&amp;amp;utm_source=producthunt-atom-posts-feed"&gt;Discussion&lt;/a&gt;
        |
        &lt;a href="https://www.producthunt.com/r/dafd51d07fff21/274542?app_id=339"&gt;Link&lt;/a&gt;
      &lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    <author>
      <name>Yash Jain</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>tag:www.producthunt.com,2005:Post/274541</id>
    <published>2020-11-11T11:47:41-08:00</published>
    <updated>2020-11-12T12:40:00-08:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/silfer-bots"/>
    <title>SilFer Bots — The complete Messenger marketing chatbot building platform</title>
    <content type="html">      &lt;p&gt;
        &lt;a href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/silfer-bots?utm_campaign=producthunt-atom-posts-feed&amp;amp;utm_medium=rss-feed&amp;amp;utm_source=producthunt-atom-posts-feed"&gt;Discussion&lt;/a&gt;
        |
        &lt;a href="https://www.producthunt.com/r/91faff75ff7007/274541?app_id=339"&gt;Link&lt;/a&gt;
      &lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    <author>
      <name>Chris Messina</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>tag:www.producthunt.com,2005:Post/274539</id>
    <published>2020-11-11T11:31:18-08:00</published>
    <updated>2020-11-12T12:35:39-08:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/the-symbols-2"/>
    <title>The Symbols 2 — Design essentials icons set</title>
    <content type="html">      &lt;p&gt;
        &lt;a href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/the-symbols-2?utm_campaign=producthunt-atom-posts-feed&amp;amp;utm_medium=rss-feed&amp;amp;utm_source=producthunt-atom-posts-feed"&gt;Discussion&lt;/a&gt;
        |
        &lt;a href="https://www.producthunt.com/r/c271e414d1faeb/274539?app_id=339"&gt;Link&lt;/a&gt;
      &lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    <author>
      <name>Alexey Sekachov</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>tag:www.producthunt.com,2005:Post/274524</id>
    <published>2020-11-11T09:45:02-08:00</published>
    <updated>2020-11-12T11:27:29-08:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/brecise"/>
    <title>Brecise — Win more customers by writing better, guided proposals.</title>
    <content type="html">      &lt;p&gt;
        &amp;#8220;
        Hey Product Hunt! 👋

Happy to be here! I'm Aleks, maker of Brecise. Really excited to announce Brecise here on Product Hunt, and to be part of such a great community!

Let's get straight to the point, writing a proposal is super boring. Whenever writing one, I'd try to get a template, change the numbers, try to change the wording so it sounds more like "me", get feedback from some friends and it would go in an endless loop…

Later, after becoming better and more experienced (after losing so many projects, and being super sad about it) you'd then start working in an enterprise environment, where most of the proposals are so time-consuming, and take so much time to change just a few numbers and items here and there.

But proposals are still super important! You are directly communicating with your customer, explaining why is your solution better than the others, what problem are you solving and why they should pay you that much.

While there are existing solutions, and they do help you design, most of the time we miss the purpose of a proposal creation, which is helping your customer and conveying the message that they want to hear. 

And that's what Brecise is: 

Helping you win more customers by writing better, guided proposals. 🚀

So, how does it work?

First, you have the Brecise Proposal Visual Designer, you start off with the basic design or can even use a template!

Next, when you start writing certain proposal sections, such as your customer's problem, or solution variants, you get asked several questions, trying to guide you into the right direction to answer the problems your customer has.

Brecise provides a library of templates, where not only can you use existing best practice ones, you can actually create organization wide ones for yourself and you team.

If you need a CRM integration and are Brecise Enterprise customer, we provides integrations with the few most common ones, and have an option to request for your specific case. 

If you’d like to export yours into PDF and Word documents, its as easy as clicking just one button!

Additionally, if you want to store your documents within Google Drive, Brecise has that too. Brecise provides storage for your files as well, all encrypted and on HIPAA compliant infrastructure.

And since you are such an amazing part of the Product Hunt community and read this far, know that we are offering free 3 months early access for all of our closed beta customers! 

Excited to hear your feedback 🙌

-- Aleks

To keep up to date, visit us on Twitter @BreciseIo
        &amp;#8221;
        &lt;br&gt;
        – Aleksandar Simovic
      &lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;
        &lt;a href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/brecise?utm_campaign=producthunt-atom-posts-feed&amp;amp;utm_medium=rss-feed&amp;amp;utm_source=producthunt-atom-posts-feed"&gt;Discussion&lt;/a&gt;
        |
        &lt;a href="https://www.producthunt.com/r/0ac1b7b7450fa4/274524?app_id=339"&gt;Link&lt;/a&gt;
      &lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    <author>
      <name>Aleksandar Simovic</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>tag:www.producthunt.com,2005:Post/274519</id>
    <published>2020-11-11T09:15:32-08:00</published>
    <updated>2020-11-12T12:29:26-08:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/datapane"/>
    <title>Datapane — Build and publish interactive data reports using Python</title>
    <content type="html">      &lt;p&gt;
        &amp;#8220;
        Hello Product Hunt 👋

Datapane is an open-source framework which makes it simple to build and share data science reports from Python.

Like many others, we prefer to analyze and visualize data in Python instead of a drag and drop tool — but, we really struggled to share our results with others. You can't always send a Jupyter Notebook or Python script to the marketing team, client, or your Slack community, and you often want to present your visualizations and data as something more accessible than step-by-step notebook.

We built Datapane to be the best way to share results from Python data analyses. After importing Datapane into your existing Jupyter or Python environment, you can use plots (from libraries like Altair or Plotly), pandas DataFrames, files, and Markdown to create reports in a few lines of code, with interactive tables, grid layout, and more. 

In addition to our open source framework, we host a free public platform on https://datapane.com/ which lets you publish the reports you build on the web, so you can share them with your community, friends, or embed them into platforms like Medium. We also have a paid product specifically for companies who build and share Python reports internally or with clients. This includes features such as automated report generation, Jupyter Notebook deployment, private reports, and easy ways to discover and collaborate on data science results.

Since we built Datapane, we've had a ton of community engagement, so the best way to see what you can do with the library is to see some of the things they're building!

- Check out some of our favourite reports build with Datapane in our gallery: https://datapane.com/gallery
- And the reports which are trending in the Datapane community right now on our explore tab: https://datapane.com/explore

Now that we're launching to a wider audience, we'd love to get some feedback on how we can make the product better, and learn about what features you'd love to see in your reports.

Any questions, fire away!

Leo
        &amp;#8221;
        &lt;br&gt;
        – Leo Anthias
      &lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;
        &lt;a href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/datapane?utm_campaign=producthunt-atom-posts-feed&amp;amp;utm_medium=rss-feed&amp;amp;utm_source=producthunt-atom-posts-feed"&gt;Discussion&lt;/a&gt;
        |
        &lt;a href="https://www.producthunt.com/r/b238e304b0f7e2/274519?app_id=339"&gt;Link&lt;/a&gt;
      &lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    <author>
      <name>Leo Anthias</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>tag:www.producthunt.com,2005:Post/274510</id>
    <published>2020-11-11T07:45:03-08:00</published>
    <updated>2020-11-12T12:34:36-08:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/smart-upscaler-2-0"/>
    <title>Smart Upscaler 2.0 — Get bigger, crisper images via bulk upload and API</title>
    <content type="html">      &lt;p&gt;
        &amp;#8220;
        The smart upscaler uses AI to clean up almost any photo. Version 2.0 greatly improves access; you can now upload images in bulk rather than 1-by-1. This makes it much more practical to use for large jobs such as upscaling e-commerce photos or user generated content. We also have officially launched the API endpoint so photo enhancement can be integrated directly into your apps. Of course, along the way we have made improvements to both usability and stability, so if you were on the fence before please give it a try (and let us know what you think).

&lt;b&gt;Bulk Processing&lt;/b&gt;
Save time by uploading a batch of photos and letting us do the rest. Just sit back and we will email you once the job is done. Clean and easy upscaling for up to 4x the resolution.

&lt;b&gt;API&lt;/b&gt;
Want to enhance the quality of images in your applications, or make the most of your UGC? The Smart Upscaler now has a ready-to-use API to handle every request.
        &amp;#8221;
        &lt;br&gt;
        – Ivan
      &lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;
        &lt;a href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/smart-upscaler-2-0?utm_campaign=producthunt-atom-posts-feed&amp;amp;utm_medium=rss-feed&amp;amp;utm_source=producthunt-atom-posts-feed"&gt;Discussion&lt;/a&gt;
        |
        &lt;a href="https://www.producthunt.com/r/8fa4c87d1f7ebc/274510?app_id=339"&gt;Link&lt;/a&gt;
      &lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    <author>
      <name>Ivan</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>tag:www.producthunt.com,2005:Post/274505</id>
    <published>2020-11-11T06:26:37-08:00</published>
    <updated>2020-11-12T12:36:22-08:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/search-console-data-exporter"/>
    <title>Search Console Data Exporter — Export 25,000 rows of query data from Google Search Console</title>
    <content type="html">      &lt;p&gt;
        &amp;#8220;
        Hi there,

Want to download more than 1,000 rows of query data from Google Search Console for your site?

After a friend asked how to do this, I decided to build a free tool.

You can do lots of good things with this data such as:
- filter by CTR to find click through rate optimization opportunities
- find striking distance keywords just off page 1
- get new content and content expansion ideas

Just open the download in Excel or Google Sheets and get filtering.

I'd really appreciate it if you shared this with your colleagues and SEO buddies.
        &amp;#8221;
        &lt;br&gt;
        – Nick Swan
      &lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;
        &lt;a href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/search-console-data-exporter?utm_campaign=producthunt-atom-posts-feed&amp;amp;utm_medium=rss-feed&amp;amp;utm_source=producthunt-atom-posts-feed"&gt;Discussion&lt;/a&gt;
        |
        &lt;a href="https://www.producthunt.com/r/57948f3a5406b6/274505?app_id=339"&gt;Link&lt;/a&gt;
      &lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    <author>
      <name>Nick Swan</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>tag:www.producthunt.com,2005:Post/274503</id>
    <published>2020-11-11T06:22:20-08:00</published>
    <updated>2020-11-12T10:44:11-08:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/wrkfrce"/>
    <title>wrkfrce — A publication focused on remote work</title>
    <content type="html">      &lt;p&gt;
        &amp;#8220;
        There's a lot of WFH and remote working information scattered throughout the internet, it'll be nice to see updates, tools. and tips all in one place. Curious to see how the other types of content play out.
        &amp;#8221;
        &lt;br&gt;
        – Gabe Perez
      &lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;
        &lt;a href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/wrkfrce?utm_campaign=producthunt-atom-posts-feed&amp;amp;utm_medium=rss-feed&amp;amp;utm_source=producthunt-atom-posts-feed"&gt;Discussion&lt;/a&gt;
        |
        &lt;a href="https://www.producthunt.com/r/9e906652c21fdf/274503?app_id=339"&gt;Link&lt;/a&gt;
      &lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    <author>
      <name>Gabe Perez</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>tag:www.producthunt.com,2005:Post/274500</id>
    <published>2020-11-11T05:41:46-08:00</published>
    <updated>2020-11-12T10:27:52-08:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/travelperi-e2fb206a-e110-4334-81dd-aee64d2a9af9"/>
    <title>TravelPeri — Find top places to explore on your next foreign adventure</title>
    <content type="html">      &lt;p&gt;
        &amp;#8220;
        Hi PH,

TravelPeri is a product that I started working on last year just before the Covid-19 pandemic wreaked havoc on the travel industry. Now that we are heading towards a post-pandemic 2021, I thought of reviving the project with a few Covid-19 related updates! 

I also feel the way forward for TravelPeri would be more travel-related content (user-generated?) in addition to the current features it offers - so I would be willing to consider any partnerships/collaborations with content-creators/writers/bloggers etc... 
Looking forward for your feedback!

A detailed outline of what the current product offers:

1.) A curated list of nearly 1000 bucket-list worthy tourist attractions from 40+ countries made accessible via an interactive map. 

2.) Seamlessly locate Booking.com rentals around each listing via a map-widget with price details.

3.) Up to-date Covid-19 statistics made available in each country page.

4.) Ability to sort the curated list of attractions in each country by travel time - based on your current location or a desired city/locality.

5.) Reference links to TripAdvisor reviews and Google map coordinates for each listing.

Read more @: https://www.travelperi.com/FAQ
Contact: contact@travelperi.com
        &amp;#8221;
        &lt;br&gt;
        – Hasitha Chandrasekara
      &lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;
        &lt;a href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/travelperi-e2fb206a-e110-4334-81dd-aee64d2a9af9?utm_campaign=producthunt-atom-posts-feed&amp;amp;utm_medium=rss-feed&amp;amp;utm_source=producthunt-atom-posts-feed"&gt;Discussion&lt;/a&gt;
        |
        &lt;a href="https://www.producthunt.com/r/5441d696ea23e7/274500?app_id=339"&gt;Link&lt;/a&gt;
      &lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    <author>
      <name>Hasitha Chandrasekara</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>tag:www.producthunt.com,2005:Post/274470</id>
    <published>2020-11-11T01:26:24-08:00</published>
    <updated>2020-11-12T10:29:32-08:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/hackerdaily"/>
    <title>HackerDaily — A less addictive Hacker News</title>
    <content type="html">      &lt;p&gt;
        &amp;#8220;
        Hi everyone!

I am studying Energy Science, but during my free time I am learning how to program. This summer I wanted to learn some new technologies, in particular Postgres, Hasura and Tailwind. To learn these technologies in a fun way I built HackerDaily. It’s a way to read Hacker News in a more informative and less addictive way.

I love Hacker News, the problem is that, like all social platforms, it easily becomes a slot machine. Every time you look there is a new post or comment!

HackerDaily is built to alleviate this problem as well as a few others:

📅 The posts are grouped per day, starting from yesterday. So you never miss that one great article, video, or paper!
📖 The articles are readable on the site itself. No more loading of multi-MB webpages just to read a simple article.
💬 It has an improved collapsing comment system
😍 Beautiful typography (based on @adamwathan awesome typography work!)
📱 It’s a PWA, so you can install it to your homescreen and use it as an app
🌗 It has a dark mode
⌨️ It's open source (https://hackerdaily.io/opensource)

I would love to hear what you think about it! I have class today, but I'll try to answer any questions. :)
        &amp;#8221;
        &lt;br&gt;
        – Ruben van Eldik
      &lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;
        &lt;a href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/hackerdaily?utm_campaign=producthunt-atom-posts-feed&amp;amp;utm_medium=rss-feed&amp;amp;utm_source=producthunt-atom-posts-feed"&gt;Discussion&lt;/a&gt;
        |
        &lt;a href="https://www.producthunt.com/r/70d4823224878a/274470?app_id=339"&gt;Link&lt;/a&gt;
      &lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    <author>
      <name>Ruben van Eldik</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>tag:www.producthunt.com,2005:Post/274464</id>
    <published>2020-11-11T00:57:39-08:00</published>
    <updated>2020-11-12T11:59:18-08:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/kickresume-3-0"/>
    <title>Kickresume 3.0 — Build resumes. Blow minds. Get hired. Fast and easy</title>
    <content type="html">      &lt;p&gt;
        &amp;#8220;
        Building a CV from scratch can be overwhelming, there are so many decisions to make from the content itself to the presentation of it. Kickresume 3.0 is a one-stop-shop for CV creation.
        &amp;#8221;
        &lt;br&gt;
        – Thomas Schranz ⛄️
      &lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;
        &lt;a href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/kickresume-3-0?utm_campaign=producthunt-atom-posts-feed&amp;amp;utm_medium=rss-feed&amp;amp;utm_source=producthunt-atom-posts-feed"&gt;Discussion&lt;/a&gt;
        |
        &lt;a href="https://www.producthunt.com/r/7679c3946a96d6/274464?app_id=339"&gt;Link&lt;/a&gt;
      &lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    <author>
      <name>Thomas Schranz ⛄️</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>tag:www.producthunt.com,2005:Post/274458</id>
    <published>2020-11-11T00:24:02-08:00</published>
    <updated>2020-11-12T12:10:49-08:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/thieve-topics"/>
    <title>Thieve Topics — Ecommerce trends &amp; niches that are hyper relevant and rising</title>
    <content type="html">      &lt;p&gt;
        &amp;#8220;
        I love Thieve. I use it every week for finding cool new products on AlieExpress that are good quality. Now they have interesting topics that I've been wanting for ages. Nice work.
        &amp;#8221;
        &lt;br&gt;
        – Jonno Riekwel
      &lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;
        &lt;a href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/thieve-topics?utm_campaign=producthunt-atom-posts-feed&amp;amp;utm_medium=rss-feed&amp;amp;utm_source=producthunt-atom-posts-feed"&gt;Discussion&lt;/a&gt;
        |
        &lt;a href="https://www.producthunt.com/r/e3c7b260dede67/274458?app_id=339"&gt;Link&lt;/a&gt;
      &lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    <author>
      <name>Jonno Riekwel</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>tag:www.producthunt.com,2005:Post/274457</id>
    <published>2020-11-11T00:22:30-08:00</published>
    <updated>2020-11-12T11:44:46-08:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/fullstats"/>
    <title>fullStats — Detailed analytics for Gumroad</title>
    <content type="html">      &lt;p&gt;
        &amp;#8220;
        The project is in its very early stages, so if you miss anything or have any feedback (specially bad), please feel free to share it! 🙏

I'm all hears!

Why did I build fullStats?
-----
While working as a web developer I created an open source project (fullPage.js) that 3 years later allowed me to quite my full-time job and became a "little free bird", or what others call it "an entrepreneur".

I started using the Gumroad platform to sell my products (fullpage.js extensions and licenses) and I quickly realised I wasn't able to get all the information I wanted from Gumroad basic analytics. 

I wanted to know about variants of a single product, about the impact of translating my site to certain languages, my top selling products, the results of a Black Friday campaign, what price should I use for my bundles... and many more.

I tried to get the information I needed from Gumroad by doing some black magic or by using their CSV stylesheet and trying to do some "queries" on it, but it wasn't enough. It was tedious, manual, and quite basic. 

I then decided to build something on the side for my own private use so I could try to maximise my profit, minimise my efforts and understand both my products and my clients better. 

Talking with other Gumroad creators I soon realised there was a demand for this so I decided to push it a bit further, improve it even more and launch it as a product to see if this can help others too.

Why fullStats?
-----
Things that you can do are:

👉   Use filters (Country | Product | Variant)
👉   Combine filters in endless ways (UK purchases for X product and X variant)
👉   Combine filtered information (show me info for this 3 products together)
👉   Get detailed information per product and filter
👉   Inspect Refunds
👉   Inspect Affiliate sales
👉   See Gumroad fees
👉   Add marks (for example, "Increased price the 2nd of January 2020)
👉   See the top Products | Countries | Variants | Offer Codes | Refunded products...
👉   Get analytics grouped by Day of the week | day of the month | hour of day | month 
👉   Get payment information (Paypal, Card...)
👉   Average purchases per customer
👉   Average spend per customer

Soon:

👉   Compare dates
👉   Cancellations information
👉   Churn
👉   Average refunds per customer
👉   Show offer codes purchases / income in chart

Do I have to pay?
-----
It is fully free for those who make less than $300/month with Gumroad. 
And for the rest, it is quite affordable. Based on MRR too:

more than $300 MRR → $2.5/month(annually)  or $2.99/month (monthly)
more than $1K MRR → $4.16/month(annually)  or $4.99/month (monthly)
more than 10K MRR → $12.5/month(annually)  or $14.99/month (monthly)
more than 50K MRR → $82.5/month(annually)  or $99/month (monthly)

Any demo I can see ?
-----
Sure!
https://fullstats.io/demo/dashboard

How does it link with Gumroad?
-----
At the moment you can:

- Sync with Gumroad so any future purchases/refunds/cancellations will be added to the system automatically.
- Import data from a CSV file you get on Gumroad
        &amp;#8221;
        &lt;br&gt;
        – Álvaro Trigo  🐦🔥
      &lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;
        &lt;a href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/fullstats?utm_campaign=producthunt-atom-posts-feed&amp;amp;utm_medium=rss-feed&amp;amp;utm_source=producthunt-atom-posts-feed"&gt;Discussion&lt;/a&gt;
        |
        &lt;a href="https://www.producthunt.com/r/9acbdc7622061a/274457?app_id=339"&gt;Link&lt;/a&gt;
      &lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    <author>
      <name>Álvaro Trigo  🐦🔥</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>tag:www.producthunt.com,2005:Post/274454</id>
    <published>2020-11-11T00:15:22-08:00</published>
    <updated>2020-11-12T11:15:32-08:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/the-least-dangerous-to-do-list"/>
    <title>The Least Dangerous To-Do List — Because today was hard enough</title>
    <content type="html">      &lt;p&gt;
        &amp;#8220;
        After the wild success of The Most Dangerous Writing App (called "sadistic" and "brutal" by WIRED and acquired by Squibler last year), I decided to make another preposterously antithetical productivity app.

Funny enough, I've been using it myself for several months now and it still adds a moment of delight to my every day. Here is to making the world a slightly weirder place.
        &amp;#8221;
        &lt;br&gt;
        – Manu Ebert
      &lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;
        &lt;a href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/the-least-dangerous-to-do-list?utm_campaign=producthunt-atom-posts-feed&amp;amp;utm_medium=rss-feed&amp;amp;utm_source=producthunt-atom-posts-feed"&gt;Discussion&lt;/a&gt;
        |
        &lt;a href="https://www.producthunt.com/r/36d5f9795a6ebf/274454?app_id=339"&gt;Link&lt;/a&gt;
      &lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    <author>
      <name>Manu Ebert</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>tag:www.producthunt.com,2005:Post/274453</id>
    <published>2020-11-11T00:09:40-08:00</published>
    <updated>2020-11-12T10:56:24-08:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/pdf-annotator-by-good-annotations"/>
    <title>PDF Annotator by Good Annotations — Draw on your pdf online</title>
    <content type="html">      &lt;p&gt;
        &amp;#8220;
        Hi everyone, 

We're super happy to release our new PDF Editor &amp;amp; Annotation Tools Beta today! 

We've been working hard on creating an online tool that you can edit your PDF documents for free. You can use all the existing Good Annotation tools that you had before and now apply them to PDF documents. That means you can add text, draw on your PDF, annotate with arrows and our professionally designed callout elements. You can even convert your PDF files to other formats like JPG or PNG. 

We always appreciate the Product Hunt communities feedback so please please let us know what you think and how it might be useful in your workflow!

Thanks!
Perry
        &amp;#8221;
        &lt;br&gt;
        – Perry Steward
      &lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;
        &lt;a href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/pdf-annotator-by-good-annotations?utm_campaign=producthunt-atom-posts-feed&amp;amp;utm_medium=rss-feed&amp;amp;utm_source=producthunt-atom-posts-feed"&gt;Discussion&lt;/a&gt;
        |
        &lt;a href="https://www.producthunt.com/r/3faf4998170344/274453?app_id=339"&gt;Link&lt;/a&gt;
      &lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    <author>
      <name>Perry Steward</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>tag:www.producthunt.com,2005:Post/274451</id>
    <published>2020-11-11T00:00:40-08:00</published>
    <updated>2020-11-12T11:11:42-08:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/postsheet"/>
    <title>PostSheet — Send personalized emails using Google Sheets (Sheet2Email)</title>
    <content type="html">      &lt;p&gt;
        &amp;#8220;
        Hi everyone 👋

&lt;a href="https://postsheet.com/?ref=producthunt" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer"&gt;PostSheet&lt;/a&gt; is a simple tool that lets you use Google Sheets (and soon Airtable) to send personalized emails to your users, customers, or marketing list.

🤔 &lt;b&gt;Why?&lt;/b&gt;
I built PostSheet to scratch my own itch. While working on my previous startups, I regularly needed to send some kind of personalized emails to my users and I always had to use a bunch of complex scripts and tools to do that.

But now, I just prepare the data in Google Sheets, write the message in PostSheet, and hit send.

💎 &lt;b&gt;Coming soon&lt;/b&gt;
- Read from Airtable
- Read from Excel
- Beautiful HTML templates
- Extensions for Chrome/Firefox
- Send SMS messages
- Send WhatsApp messages

Please use the poll below to help me decide which one to build first. Or, leave a comment if you have any other suggestions/ideas.

🔥 &lt;b&gt;Deal&lt;/b&gt;
You can use the code PRODUCTHUNT at checkout to get 20% off your subscription. &lt;b&gt;Valid only today!&lt;/b&gt;

☝️ &lt;b&gt;One more thing&lt;/b&gt;
I'm building PostSheet in public on Twitter. Love to connect with you there: &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/soheilpro" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer"&gt;https://twitter.com/soheilpro&lt;/a&gt;


Thank you 🙏
Soheil
        &amp;#8221;
        &lt;br&gt;
        – Soheil
      &lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;
        &lt;a href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/postsheet?utm_campaign=producthunt-atom-posts-feed&amp;amp;utm_medium=rss-feed&amp;amp;utm_source=producthunt-atom-posts-feed"&gt;Discussion&lt;/a&gt;
        |
        &lt;a href="https://www.producthunt.com/r/0b3cee7d673efb/274451?app_id=339"&gt;Link&lt;/a&gt;
      &lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    <author>
      <name>Soheil</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>tag:www.producthunt.com,2005:Post/274439</id>
    <published>2020-11-10T22:23:34-08:00</published>
    <updated>2020-11-12T12:40:46-08:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/airbyte"/>
    <title>Airbyte — Replicate data in minutes with prebuilt &amp; custom connectors</title>
    <content type="html">      &lt;p&gt;
        &amp;#8220;
        Company are aggregating more and more data that are siloed into more and more tools. Data teams end up needing to building and maintaining more and more connectors to leverage their data. 

This situation is only getting worse. You need a solution like Airbyte to connect and aggregate all your data sources.

And it’s open source! 🤩
        &amp;#8221;
        &lt;br&gt;
        – Nicolas Grenié
      &lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;
        &lt;a href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/airbyte?utm_campaign=producthunt-atom-posts-feed&amp;amp;utm_medium=rss-feed&amp;amp;utm_source=producthunt-atom-posts-feed"&gt;Discussion&lt;/a&gt;
        |
        &lt;a href="https://www.producthunt.com/r/bf61cc2069dc38/274439?app_id=339"&gt;Link&lt;/a&gt;
      &lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    <author>
      <name>Nicolas Grenié</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>tag:www.producthunt.com,2005:Post/274437</id>
    <published>2020-11-10T22:18:32-08:00</published>
    <updated>2020-11-12T12:29:49-08:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/spaces-f6c925da-0b08-433d-9348-14bdd162ea8b"/>
    <title>~spaces~ — Spatial social networking</title>
    <content type="html">      &lt;p&gt;
        &amp;#8220;
        Hey everyone! I built this new social network that I hope y'all will like. 

Spaces is all about creation and experiences. You get from it exactly what you put into it. No more doom-scrolling through endless feeds or learning not-so-cool dances to not-so-cool songs. In Spaces you can hang out with your friends as you would in real life. Invite them over to your world and show them off how your house looks or the new hat you just bought. Find yourself immersed in this new universe you can help create.

Shoot me a message at pablo[at]spacesapp.xyz if you have any feedback, comments or just wanna chat.

~~~~hope y'all have fun~~~~

Pablo.
        &amp;#8221;
        &lt;br&gt;
        – Pablo Ar 🌐
      &lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;
        &lt;a href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/spaces-f6c925da-0b08-433d-9348-14bdd162ea8b?utm_campaign=producthunt-atom-posts-feed&amp;amp;utm_medium=rss-feed&amp;amp;utm_source=producthunt-atom-posts-feed"&gt;Discussion&lt;/a&gt;
        |
        &lt;a href="https://www.producthunt.com/r/ee83513ce1836a/274437?app_id=339"&gt;Link&lt;/a&gt;
      &lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    <author>
      <name>Pablo Ar 🌐</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>tag:www.producthunt.com,2005:Post/274428</id>
    <published>2020-11-10T20:49:22-08:00</published>
    <updated>2020-11-12T12:40:05-08:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/xpression-camera"/>
    <title>xpression camera — Become anyone on Zoom, Twitch, or any streaming video</title>
    <content type="html">      &lt;p&gt;
        &amp;#8220;
        Really impressed by the quality of xpression camera's results... their custom models are capable of creating very convincing digital face puppets!
        &amp;#8221;
        &lt;br&gt;
        – Chris Messina
      &lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;
        &lt;a href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/xpression-camera?utm_campaign=producthunt-atom-posts-feed&amp;amp;utm_medium=rss-feed&amp;amp;utm_source=producthunt-atom-posts-feed"&gt;Discussion&lt;/a&gt;
        |
        &lt;a href="https://www.producthunt.com/r/fad8ccbd2eca1f/274428?app_id=339"&gt;Link&lt;/a&gt;
      &lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    <author>
      <name>Chris Messina</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>tag:www.producthunt.com,2005:Post/274422</id>
    <published>2020-11-10T18:36:26-08:00</published>
    <updated>2020-11-12T06:40:54-08:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/skyroam-solis-lite"/>
    <title>Skyroam Solis Lite — Small yet powerful global pocket WiFi</title>
    <content type="html">      &lt;p&gt;
        &amp;#8220;
        I got this when I started WFH as a back up in case the internet went out or I was traveling. I've used this for days on end while traveling and it's pretty impressive. The signal lets me go throughout the day without any to little interruption and the battery lasts like 2 days without charge. 

It's not perfect, but it's definitely a handy tool to have if you're a modern nomad or tech traveler.
        &amp;#8221;
        &lt;br&gt;
        – Gabe Perez
      &lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;
        &lt;a href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/skyroam-solis-lite?utm_campaign=producthunt-atom-posts-feed&amp;amp;utm_medium=rss-feed&amp;amp;utm_source=producthunt-atom-posts-feed"&gt;Discussion&lt;/a&gt;
        |
        &lt;a href="https://www.producthunt.com/r/7e215421e31b1f/274422?app_id=339"&gt;Link&lt;/a&gt;
      &lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    <author>
      <name>Gabe Perez</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>tag:www.producthunt.com,2005:Post/274421</id>
    <published>2020-11-10T18:32:11-08:00</published>
    <updated>2020-11-12T12:32:43-08:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/zipcan"/>
    <title>Zipcan — Add video chat inside your website or application in seconds</title>
    <content type="html">      &lt;p&gt;
        &amp;#8220;
        Think about it — at one point, generic email was what everyone had (@aol.com, @prodigy.com, @gmail.com)... but gradually we moved to branded/company/personal domains that we owned.

We're in the same era when it comes to video calls — relying on third parties like Zoom or Google Meet and others to provide what is becoming the de facto way for people to communicate. 

Zipcan makes it possible to use your own URL/domain for video calls. Indeed, here's mine! 

https://chrismessina.me/call-me
        &amp;#8221;
        &lt;br&gt;
        – Chris Messina
      &lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;
        &lt;a href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/zipcan?utm_campaign=producthunt-atom-posts-feed&amp;amp;utm_medium=rss-feed&amp;amp;utm_source=producthunt-atom-posts-feed"&gt;Discussion&lt;/a&gt;
        |
        &lt;a href="https://www.producthunt.com/r/4dce220e3e5659/274421?app_id=339"&gt;Link&lt;/a&gt;
      &lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    <author>
      <name>Chris Messina</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>tag:www.producthunt.com,2005:Post/274420</id>
    <published>2020-11-10T18:08:24-08:00</published>
    <updated>2020-11-12T12:31:22-08:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/my-desk-tour-2"/>
    <title>My Desk Tour — The place for WFH desk inspiration.</title>
    <content type="html">      &lt;p&gt;
        &amp;#8220;
        Whatsup PH! 

Came up with the idea for a site about desk setups when I was looking for a mouse this summer. Got lost in review sites, and decided it was best to just ask people what mouses they used. 

Reddit (r/MouseReview and r/battlestations) came to the rescue, but I thought it might be cool to make a site dedicated for this kind of thing!

I hope you find some inspiration from browsing around, and feel free to add your desk into the mix :)
        &amp;#8221;
        &lt;br&gt;
        – Jonathan Cai
      &lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;
        &lt;a href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/my-desk-tour-2?utm_campaign=producthunt-atom-posts-feed&amp;amp;utm_medium=rss-feed&amp;amp;utm_source=producthunt-atom-posts-feed"&gt;Discussion&lt;/a&gt;
        |
        &lt;a href="https://www.producthunt.com/r/177f191ee8ab0f/274420?app_id=339"&gt;Link&lt;/a&gt;
      &lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    <author>
      <name>Jonathan Cai</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>tag:www.producthunt.com,2005:Post/274418</id>
    <published>2020-11-10T16:52:56-08:00</published>
    <updated>2020-11-12T08:47:30-08:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/valotalive"/>
    <title>Valotalive — Workplace digital signage software</title>
    <content type="html">      &lt;p&gt;
        &lt;a href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/valotalive?utm_campaign=producthunt-atom-posts-feed&amp;amp;utm_medium=rss-feed&amp;amp;utm_source=producthunt-atom-posts-feed"&gt;Discussion&lt;/a&gt;
        |
        &lt;a href="https://www.producthunt.com/r/7312fd7fe67078/274418?app_id=339"&gt;Link&lt;/a&gt;
      &lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    <author>
      <name>Tomi Paajanen</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>tag:www.producthunt.com,2005:Post/274415</id>
    <published>2020-11-10T16:16:21-08:00</published>
    <updated>2020-11-12T12:40:22-08:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/humanloop"/>
    <title>Humanloop — Train state-of-the-art language AI in the browser</title>
    <content type="html">      &lt;p&gt;
        &lt;a href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/humanloop?utm_campaign=producthunt-atom-posts-feed&amp;amp;utm_medium=rss-feed&amp;amp;utm_source=producthunt-atom-posts-feed"&gt;Discussion&lt;/a&gt;
        |
        &lt;a href="https://www.producthunt.com/r/d33528f6eda766/274415?app_id=339"&gt;Link&lt;/a&gt;
      &lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    <author>
      <name>Kat Manalac</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>tag:www.producthunt.com,2005:Post/274411</id>
    <published>2020-11-10T14:06:24-08:00</published>
    <updated>2020-11-12T10:18:38-08:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/watchmaking-kits-by-rotate"/>
    <title>Watchmaking Kits by ROTATE — All-in-one kits to build a mechanical watch. </title>
    <content type="html">      &lt;p&gt;
        &amp;#8220;
        Hi there! I'm the founder of Rotate Watches. I first came up with the idea for it back in 2017, when I attempted to assemble my first mechanical watch. I discovered that there was no such thing as an all-inclusive watchmaking kit and had to jump through hoops and hurdles to put together that first watch. I got to work building the exact kit I wish I had when building my first watch. 

A brief history - we officially launched in October 2019 via Kickstarter where we raised 600% of our goal (over $91k). Since then, we've been selling live on our website, have been featured in publications like the New York Times, and have expanded our product selection to other watch parts and accessories. We're sold in all Fry's Electronics stores nationwide and do frequent partnerships with other companies such as Touch of Modern. You can read more about us on www.rotatewatches.com. 

I'd love to hear any kind of feedback on Rotate! All ideas and suggestions are welcome. Thank you!!
        &amp;#8221;
        &lt;br&gt;
        – Jennifer Zhang
      &lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;
        &lt;a href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/watchmaking-kits-by-rotate?utm_campaign=producthunt-atom-posts-feed&amp;amp;utm_medium=rss-feed&amp;amp;utm_source=producthunt-atom-posts-feed"&gt;Discussion&lt;/a&gt;
        |
        &lt;a href="https://www.producthunt.com/r/bd4ef21c365762/274411?app_id=339"&gt;Link&lt;/a&gt;
      &lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    <author>
      <name>Jennifer Zhang</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>tag:www.producthunt.com,2005:Post/274404</id>
    <published>2020-11-10T12:52:55-08:00</published>
    <updated>2020-11-12T08:53:19-08:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/scribbble-io"/>
    <title>Scribbble.io — A blogging platform for developers</title>
    <content type="html">      &lt;p&gt;
        &lt;a href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/scribbble-io?utm_campaign=producthunt-atom-posts-feed&amp;amp;utm_medium=rss-feed&amp;amp;utm_source=producthunt-atom-posts-feed"&gt;Discussion&lt;/a&gt;
        |
        &lt;a href="https://www.producthunt.com/r/b1302dde0d3dbb/274404?app_id=339"&gt;Link&lt;/a&gt;
      &lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    <author>
      <name>Ward Poel</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>tag:www.producthunt.com,2005:Post/274402</id>
    <published>2020-11-10T12:16:12-08:00</published>
    <updated>2020-11-12T12:30:57-08:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/wooli"/>
    <title>Wooli — WooCommerce store essential metrics in your Mac menu bar.</title>
    <content type="html">      &lt;p&gt;
        &lt;a href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/wooli?utm_campaign=producthunt-atom-posts-feed&amp;amp;utm_medium=rss-feed&amp;amp;utm_source=producthunt-atom-posts-feed"&gt;Discussion&lt;/a&gt;
        |
        &lt;a href="https://www.producthunt.com/r/16f42a76c77efc/274402?app_id=339"&gt;Link&lt;/a&gt;
      &lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    <author>
      <name>Sinisa Komlenic</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>tag:www.producthunt.com,2005:Post/274398</id>
    <published>2020-11-10T11:13:56-08:00</published>
    <updated>2020-11-12T12:10:04-08:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/if-you-bought-xyz"/>
    <title>If You Bought XYZ — How much money you would have made investing in the past.</title>
    <content type="html">      &lt;p&gt;
        &lt;a href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/if-you-bought-xyz?utm_campaign=producthunt-atom-posts-feed&amp;amp;utm_medium=rss-feed&amp;amp;utm_source=producthunt-atom-posts-feed"&gt;Discussion&lt;/a&gt;
        |
        &lt;a href="https://www.producthunt.com/r/3061863b1468a1/274398?app_id=339"&gt;Link&lt;/a&gt;
      &lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    <author>
      <name>Naeem Noor</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>tag:www.producthunt.com,2005:Post/274397</id>
    <published>2020-11-10T11:04:20-08:00</published>
    <updated>2020-11-12T12:33:47-08:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/the-new-macbook-pro"/>
    <title>The New Macbook Pro — A new Macbook Pro with the M1 chip</title>
    <content type="html">      &lt;p&gt;
        &amp;#8220;
        I hope this doesn't suffer from the same thermal issues as the previous MBP. Also saw Among us demoed on this 👀 Apple also launched today: &lt;a href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/the-new-mac-mini" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer"&gt;The New Mac Mini&lt;/a&gt; and the &lt;a href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/the-new-macbook-air" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer"&gt;new Macbook Air&lt;/a&gt;
        &amp;#8221;
        &lt;br&gt;
        – Aaron  O'Leary
      &lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;
        &lt;a href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/the-new-macbook-pro?utm_campaign=producthunt-atom-posts-feed&amp;amp;utm_medium=rss-feed&amp;amp;utm_source=producthunt-atom-posts-feed"&gt;Discussion&lt;/a&gt;
        |
        &lt;a href="https://www.producthunt.com/r/692268ccfa7228/274397?app_id=339"&gt;Link&lt;/a&gt;
      &lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    <author>
      <name>Aaron  O'Leary</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>tag:www.producthunt.com,2005:Post/274395</id>
    <published>2020-11-10T10:57:49-08:00</published>
    <updated>2020-11-12T12:15:10-08:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/the-new-macbook-air"/>
    <title>The New Macbook Air — A new MacBook Air with the M1 chip</title>
    <content type="html">      &lt;p&gt;
        &amp;#8220;
        That M1 chip looks incredible, the price point is pretty good also, like it's still relatively accessible
        &amp;#8221;
        &lt;br&gt;
        – Aaron  O'Leary
      &lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;
        &lt;a href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/the-new-macbook-air?utm_campaign=producthunt-atom-posts-feed&amp;amp;utm_medium=rss-feed&amp;amp;utm_source=producthunt-atom-posts-feed"&gt;Discussion&lt;/a&gt;
        |
        &lt;a href="https://www.producthunt.com/r/91de12ef253895/274395?app_id=339"&gt;Link&lt;/a&gt;
      &lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    <author>
      <name>Aaron  O'Leary</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>tag:www.producthunt.com,2005:Post/274394</id>
    <published>2020-11-10T10:50:02-08:00</published>
    <updated>2020-11-12T09:09:00-08:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/the-new-mac-mini"/>
    <title>The New Mac Mini — Apple's newest Mac Mini with the latest M1 chip</title>
    <content type="html">      &lt;p&gt;
        &lt;a href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/the-new-mac-mini?utm_campaign=producthunt-atom-posts-feed&amp;amp;utm_medium=rss-feed&amp;amp;utm_source=producthunt-atom-posts-feed"&gt;Discussion&lt;/a&gt;
        |
        &lt;a href="https://www.producthunt.com/r/dd4f707463657b/274394?app_id=339"&gt;Link&lt;/a&gt;
      &lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    <author>
      <name>NaveenKumar Namachivayam</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>tag:www.producthunt.com,2005:Post/274393</id>
    <published>2020-11-10T10:43:56-08:00</published>
    <updated>2020-11-12T12:38:45-08:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/oi-oi-hand-drawn-illustrations"/>
    <title>oi-oi hand-drawn illustrations — Customizable illustrations for websites and applications</title>
    <content type="html">      &lt;p&gt;
        &amp;#8220;
        Hello 👋

I’m happy to announce that oi-oi 20 vector, minimalistic and customizable illustrations have just been released. As a creator of Whoooa! https://www.producthunt.com/posts/whoooa-illustrations I have decided to create another set of illustrations but this time in a different style.

Creating a unique style is hard and we wanted to achieve something that will set your projects apart. Our handmade illustrations focus on the most wanted subjects for startups, various types of businesses, social media, marketing, web, and mobile applications.

The pack includes a template for Sketch, Figma, Adobe XD, so you can change colors at once for all 20 illustrations with just a few clicks to fit the color palette of your product or brand.

&lt;strong&gt;See how it works in: &lt;/strong&gt;
Sketch - https://yellowww1983.wistia.com/medias/tmgy1plgv7 
Figma - https://yellowww1983.wistia.com/medias/415uya9ys4
Adobe XD - https://yellowww1983.wistia.com/medias/easn5ejrd2

&lt;strong&gt;Available in the following formats:&lt;/strong&gt; ai, sketch, fig, adobe xd, eps, svg, png, jpg

&lt;strong&gt;Compatible with:&lt;/strong&gt; Adobe Illustrator, Sketch, Figma, Adobe XD, Photoshop, Affinity Designer, and more.

&lt;strong&gt;You will get:&lt;/strong&gt;
- 20 vector illustrations 
- Vector + raster formats for all design software
- Free lifetime updates 
- Personal &amp;amp; commercial license
- A template for Sketch, Figma, Adobe XD for changing colors

We have a &lt;strong&gt;25% discount&lt;/strong&gt; for PH buyers with this code &lt;strong&gt;oioi-25-ph&lt;/strong&gt; (you can apply it at checkout) or you can simply use this URL https://gumroad.com/l/LtatR/oioi-25-ph

Enjoy and spread the love 💜
        &amp;#8221;
        &lt;br&gt;
        – Greg Dlubacz
      &lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;
        &lt;a href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/oi-oi-hand-drawn-illustrations?utm_campaign=producthunt-atom-posts-feed&amp;amp;utm_medium=rss-feed&amp;amp;utm_source=producthunt-atom-posts-feed"&gt;Discussion&lt;/a&gt;
        |
        &lt;a href="https://www.producthunt.com/r/d5fa69eb9fccfb/274393?app_id=339"&gt;Link&lt;/a&gt;
      &lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    <author>
      <name>Greg Dlubacz</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>tag:www.producthunt.com,2005:Post/274391</id>
    <published>2020-11-10T10:13:26-08:00</published>
    <updated>2020-11-12T09:37:56-08:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/covid-19-personal-risk-explorer"/>
    <title>COVID-19 Personal Risk Explorer — See how COVID19 affects your life risks at home or traveling</title>
    <content type="html">      &lt;p&gt;
        &amp;#8220;
        Our commercial product (Safe-xplore) is used by travel risk intelligence and executive protection teams of some of the world's wealthiest and most powerful brands and executives - but we wanted to share our data &amp;amp; know-how in a free, public-interest format, that would enable everyone to better understand this urgent health risk, and make safer, smarter decisions. So here it is!
        &amp;#8221;
        &lt;br&gt;
        – Filippo
      &lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;
        &lt;a href="https://www.producthunt.com/posts/covid-19-personal-risk-explorer?utm_campaign=producthunt-atom-posts-feed&amp;amp;utm_medium=rss-feed&amp;amp;utm_source=producthunt-atom-posts-feed"&gt;Discussion&lt;/a&gt;
        |
        &lt;a href="https://www.producthunt.com/r/5da74b98ee2e77/274391?app_id=339"&gt;Link&lt;/a&gt;
      &lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    <author>
      <name>Filippo</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
</feed>
